<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GeekyHub</title>
    <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GeekyHub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](http://gohugo.io).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 17:51:16 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.geekyhub.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Simple WhatsApp bot in Python using Selenium</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/making-a-whatsapp-bot-using-python-selenium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 17:51:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/making-a-whatsapp-bot-using-python-selenium/</guid>
      <description>Selenium is a web automation package available for all popular languages. To know more about selenium you can refer to official Selenium docs. Here, we will be making a simple WhatsApp bot using Python and Selenium which will reply the current time for every message.
Installing Selenium So, first of all, we need to install Selenium for Python by running following command in terminal.
 pip install selenium  Selenium also requires a driver to interface with the chosen browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some &#39;cool&#39; things Visual Studio Code can do you may haven&#39;t known</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/hidden-features-of-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 16:35:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/hidden-features-of-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Mircosoft&amp;rsquo;s Visual Studio Code has proven to be the dark horse of code editors. Don&amp;rsquo;t confuse yourself by seeing Microsoft as it is completely free, open source and MIT licensed.
Even being late to the party, it has attracted enough users. The reason behind this is a perfect balance between speed, features, and hackability.
If you are new to this editor, these are some features you should be known to improve your productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear CS Freshman, Kali Linux is not what you are thinking</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/you-shouldnt-begin-linux-with-kali/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 04:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/you-shouldnt-begin-linux-with-kali/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post is intended for college Freshmans those who have little or no experience with Linux. If you are an experienced Linux user you may skip the post safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-linux&#34;&gt;What is Linux?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linux is basically a term to refer all the distributions (or say OS) based on Linux Kernel collectively. some of its notable distributions are Ubuntu, Fedora, Arch, your favorite Kali Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-may-you-have-heard-about-kali-linux&#34;&gt;Where may you have heard about Kali Linux?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bet it is your friend or someone elder who said to you that Kali Linux can hack computers. I have seen students being obsessed with this distro without knowing anything about Linux.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://www.geekyhub.in/images/kalimeme.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Easiest way to become a Hacker&lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Now hack is a stupid term. Most of the people think that it something by which you can access information without proper permission.  No, my friend, the term is much broader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;hack&lt;/strong&gt; is defined as &amp;ldquo;a tip, trick, or efficient method for doing or managing something&amp;rdquo; or in the Indian language, we say &lt;em&gt;Jugaad&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Pen is great Windows Ink workspace alternative for Windows 7</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/screen_sketch_older_windows_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/screen_sketch_older_windows_7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Windows Ink workspace is great addition to Windows 10. Due to this tool, annotating has never been easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Windows 7 is still rock solid in the marked. Apart from corporate users many personal users are on Windows 7 which include my relatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I use thier PC, only option to achieve the screen sketch is to take screenshot in paint and draw on it using pain. This method is not bad but also doesn&amp;rsquo;t goes smoothly with my work flow. Mainly because it involes too much clicks
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>