<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GeekyHub</title>
    <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GeekyHub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](http://gohugo.io).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 23:13:25 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.geekyhub.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Pen is great Windows Ink workspace alternative for Windows 7</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/screen_sketch_older_windows_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/screen_sketch_older_windows_7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Windows Ink workspace is great addition to Windows 10. Due to this tool, annotating has never been easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Windows 7 is still rock solid in the marked. Apart from corporate users many personal users are on Windows 7 which include my relatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I use thier PC, only option to achieve the screen sketch is to take screenshot in paint and draw on it using pain. This method is not bad but also doesn&amp;rsquo;t goes smoothly with my work flow. Mainly because it involes too much clicks
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my new blog</title>
      <link>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/starting-a-new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geekyhub.in/post/starting-a-new-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had my last paper of this semester&amp;rsquo;s exams just a day before yesterday. If I can speak my mind, this semester has been very boring. Most of the subjects were a just compilation of the subjects I have read in previous semesters which made me lukewarm about studies. I am just hopeful that I&amp;rsquo;ll get pass marks in all subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In course of examination, I stumbled upon my lost forgotten blog on &lt;a href=&#34;http://geekyhub.blogspot.in&#34;&gt;Blogger&lt;/a&gt;  . It didn&amp;rsquo;t take much time to realize that the blog is very embarrassing, done like a 10 to 5 job. A personal touch cannot be found on that blog. So, I decided to do a fresh start after examinations and this new blog is my another effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>